很感谢大家的光临
这里是纽约的Pierre酒店
感谢数百万的在线观看的观众
特别是在大陆的朋友
这个演讲就是为中国的民众和美国的民众准备的，
(所以呢)我也想欢迎一下在大陆的观众
去年的一整年
全球的媒体广泛报道了下面两个事件
第一件在今年春天发生在伦敦
另一件在几周前发生在土耳其
第一个事件是在伦敦
毒死了一个俄罗斯的持不同政见者
另一件是几周前
华盛顿邮报的专栏记者，卡舒吉在土耳其(疑)遭杀害
这两个悲剧事件，都在国际媒体上引起了轩然大波
可我们下面要谈的，也就是郭文贵要介绍给大家的
(跟那两个事件相比)可以说更为震惊
几百位，甚至上千位顶尖的中国人
失踪
进监狱
自杀
离奇地死亡
或者财产被没收
被抄家
可是媒体却对(这些事)集体失声，并且好像全都无动于衷
这并不是一个或两个的孤立事件
这些人也不是所谓的上不了报纸的小人物
他们来自企业界
金融界
政界
军界
是来自各行各业的精英。也是一个个原本鲜活的生命
让人惊讶的是在信息如此发达的今天，
媒体持续地无视这些(事件)，媒很好地做到了“万马齐喑”
但今天我们要结束这种现象
因为有个人，他将要站出来，呼喊：
他不准备容忍这些
他要用他的一切,来揭示真相
去保证中国的民众，不再继续遭受中国共产党
以及中共高官的奴役
今天(我们要揭示CCP的)疯狂以及进行问责
世界上的很多人，尤其是所谓的富人，现在要开始认清一点
就是中国共产党和它的高官
在过去的十到二十年在财务上，印钱，增加负债的疯狂行为
我认为会导致一场金融危机
郭文贵下面要讲的例子可以说明这一点
我们有这样一个，很可能是世界上最大的金融公司之一海航集团
从2014年到2018年，这家公司基本上是从一家非常小的公司创建
在西方一些大的金融机构和西方金融界高手的帮助和支持下
成为世界上最大的金融机构
必须要问的问题是
这有多么恣意鲁莽
谁受益于此？
谁拥有这些财富？
谁从中国人那里拿走了这些资产？
谁从中获利了？
谁又装作没看到？
另外，海航集团的领导人在不合时宜的时候突然死亡
今天你将看到郭先生和其他调查人员对此事进行的调查
调查材料将交给有关当局，我们有很多很多问题
到底这是怎么回事？
法治是最有力的手段之一
海航所犯的错误
金融机构和那些利用海航恣意扩长而获利的奸商所犯的错误
是他们称Miles Kwok骗子
然后他们上法庭诉讼Miles Kwok诽谤
他们会发现这对他们来说是一个致命的错误
因为在美国，我们有法治
Miles Kwok今天会告知大家，他准备在一些领域采取行动
包括非常积极的反诉讼，以及非常积极的反诽谤诉讼
因为你今天会看到
Miles Kwok所说的海航
及中共和中共领导人
是如何怂恿海航的恣意扩张这些事
都是真的
你们今天将通过披露的事实看到这些西方金融机构
在海航事件开始暴露时，像老鼠离开沉船一样逃离
更重要的是
Miles Kwok将在演讲结束时对中国人民和中国受害者的人说
他正准备建立一个一亿美元的基金 - 法治基金
它的主要目的是帮助中国受害人家人，受害者，失踪者的朋友
被监禁的人
以及那些从40层建筑上掉下来（所谓）自杀的人
和财产被没收的人
郭先生已准备好成立并资助一个基金
不仅用来搜集信息帮助在中国大陆的受害者
还要追究这些在西方的
特别是纽约，伦敦和其他城市金融中心机构
追究它们资助怂恿这种鲁莽的行为的责任
首先郭先生要做一个介绍
接着一部分参与调查的人会简短发言
在问答之后, 我们也会准备回答媒体更多的问题
请大家记住，我们这个刚刚开始的调查过程可能需要很多年
因为目前这个状况是几十年形成的
但是今天我们拿出海航的例子
这家普通的公司
现在成了世界上最大的金融公司
他的领导者却在两个月前离奇的死去
却没有任何人对此进行讨论
我想我可以为郭先生来说
这个状况今天结束
新的一天开始了
下面有请郭先生
在开始提问之前
请帮我回到Miles刚刚提到的即将采取行动的那一页
请回到那一页
我想重温一下这一部分
因为这里面的一些分析
很多人是第一次接触到这些信息
我想说的几点是
你们目前所看到的关于调查方面的信息
只是郭先生以及他团队所提供的一些非常表面的信息
你可以看到他们已经得到了在酒店里的录像
得到了数小时的证人采访
这些都只是非常表层的东西
来自法国的 Vince Gaetan先生也加入了我们
他是第一个到达案发现场的目击者
他随后可以与媒体交流
还有TONY先生
他带领的调查团队六次前往事发地点
这是一个非常彻底的调查开始
当你看到详细信息时你会相当震惊
我们再来看一遍
这是我认为最震惊的部分
像我之前说的有些人可能没有注意到开始的部分
在伦敦的时候
有针对俄罗斯公民的毒杀事件
不幸的是
在土耳其也发生了关于专栏作家卡舒其的案子
这些都引起了世界轰动
that they can do whatever they think is necessary
to go the various cities to make sure people in those cities and communities, get the full briefing.
He also committed to the gravy he can't go overseas and spread this
Now  Miles Guo was pretty pretty big cheque today, that's gonna have to be cashed
principally he is saying that NHA and associated with the Chinese Community Party is not just an
intelligence asset but money laundering asset of senior officials with the CCP and the company.
And he is highly confident that when all the information is turned over and using the rule
of law of the American courts
and that will be shown in the transparency that one needs.
It's shocking to me that it is taken to November of 2018 for this to happen,
The recklessness of the Chinese Community Party‘s senior officials and the recklessness of the financial
institution and senior executives in those institutions to allow this to happen is nothing short of
stunning.
And we would like to do we run over the time we will take questions, and then we're gonna to make
you a full access to the medias have full access to Miles to Mr.Gittan from France to Tony investigators
to myself
afterwards ,you would like to take a few questions what we are gonna do is, I want you to
identify yourself, I know of a few of you but please identify yourself so the livestream audiences can
hear you, and we're gonna take, we're gonna make sure the translated
so Miles can answer the questions, I like to start with Sasha are gone from a columnist from the
South China Morning post.
Mr. Steve :I have to correct you that's not the case, I just write for them.
anywey I think I earn my right to tap the first question since I almost lost my job
Since you start this.
Well anyway the question is that Miles Guo what you said today and what you said in the past year and half,
was pretty incredible.
and you remembered in the beginning in Chinese is that "审贼一样审了两天“ becuase I did not belive
a lot of it,
And now I have been doing a lot of investigation on this and working on so
what suprise me is that I don't see a lot of media attention media report on what you said becuase it is
pretty incredible .
And as a media person I wonder how much pressure the Chinese goverment put on the international media.
In my case I have dozens of my friends in China being arrested
one of them actualy Steve you may have your first case my fried Dr.刘鹏飞 last name
刘L-I-U 鹏飞
he spread your word he is my friend he was arrested last September he still in jail he has been
tortured, very miserable story，
I hope you guys will pay attention to him,but you know， question to him to and his friends, dozens of
my friends to  pressure me to shut up,
so I wonder if other people other members of the international media also you know suffered such pressure
and otherwise why don't we see more report on what you said
actual and another question two, one more question is that I read some documents and I read the New York
times report,
it said that the Chinese government was willing to pay three billion US dollars to get you back, do you
have more details of that imformation and in what way they can pay the three billion dollars
and one more question to Mr. Bannon is that is the Trump administration aware of you know what's happening here?
thank you